Murtaza Kankroliwala

Software Developer

I have 2.5 years of professional expertise in full stack web and app development. React for the front end, Python for the back end, and Flutter for app development make up my current preferred tech stack. Searching for opportunities to get experience and learn new tech stacks.



mkankroli3@gmail.com

+91 9819542253

Mumbai, India

mkankroliportfolio.netlify.app/



linkedin.com/in/murtaza-kankroliwala-938514168

in

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer LogisticsNow

10/2020 - Present

Mulund, Maharashtra, India

Digital Backbone of logistics to help Transporters and Manufacturers to build a technology enabled transportation and logistics business.

Work Description:

- Working as a Full Stack Developer. (Tech Stack: React, python, Microsoft Azure (CosmosDB, Function Apps, SignalR, Form Recognizer, Redis etc.))
- Creating UI Design using balsamiq, figma and draw.io.
- Working on Live Web Application for Transporters and Manufacturers for Supply Chain and Logistics Management. Handling Indents, Benchmarking, Spot Enquiries, Reverse Auctions, Procurements, etc.
- Mobile Application Development using flutter for LORRI Spot Enquiries.

Team Leader for Full Stack App and Web Developer Intern Upcloud Technology

04/2020 - 10/2020

Platform for Digital Healthcare Industry

Work Description

- App Development Using Flutter
- Web Application Development
- Tech leader for App and Web developer

Associate Software Engineer Intern LogisticsNow

12/2019 - 03/2020

Mulund, Mumbai

Remote

Digital Backbone of logistics to help Transporters and Manufacturers to build a technology enabled transportation and logistics business.

Achievements/Tasks

- Android Application as a basic app test
- Web Application Front-end developement for their Website Using ReactJs mostly on Maps
- Testing of the system and log the bugs and suggestions

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Computer Engineering

K. J. Somaiya College of Engg., Somaiya Vidyanagar, Vidyvihar

06/2017 - 10/2020 7.89

Diploma in Computer Technology

M.M. Babasaheb Gawde Institute of Technology

08/2014 - 06/2017 86.24

SKILLS

ReactJS Python

Flutter App Development Nodejs HTML

CSS BootStrap App Development

FrontEnd Development Javascript

PERSONAL PROJECTS

B.Tech Project (06/2019 - 06/2020)

 Fire Extinguishing Support System for fire station where user can report the fire station using app or using IoT if Alarms the nearest Fire Station for help

Diploma Project (06/2016 - 04/2017)

 TiffinVilla: Android Application to get user the home made food.

NGO Project (01/2019 - 04/2019)

A Mini Project in Third Year Engineering.

Inventory Management (11/2020 - 01/2021)

 Short App Development for Rockford's where the drivers add their stock details and maintains transfer.

ACHIEVEMENTS

LogisticsNow: Spot Award

For Estimation and completion of work on estimated time.

3rd in Technical Paper Presentation

For TiffinVilla Project, Android App to send the tiffin from one place to another

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Gujarati - Speaking

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Hybrid App Development

Full Stack Development

AI/ML